Soviet Union Unregistered Baptists Subject Files, Inclusive: 1948-2011, undated, Bulk: 1960-1989
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Samizdat, 1961-1987, 2011, undated; 2
  - Unregistered Baptist Church Administration. Statements and Circulars, 1978 July, 1982 February (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church-State Relations, 1968, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Registration of Churches by the State, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (1 of 24), 1963, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (2 of 24), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (3 of 24), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (4 of 24), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (5 of 24), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (6 of 24), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (7 of 24), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (8 of 24), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (9 of 24), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (10 of 24), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (11 of 24), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (12 of 24), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (13 of 24), 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (14 of 24), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (15 of 24), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (16 of 24), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (17 of 24), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (18 of 24), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (19 of 24), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (20 of 24), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (21 of 24), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (22 of 24), 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (23 of 24), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. General (24 of 24), 1981-1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. New Year Appeal from the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christian Baptist Prisoners, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Harassment, 1971-1977 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Physical Assault (1 of 2), 1964, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Physical Assault (2 of 2), 1975-1976, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Disruption of Meetings and Prayer Groups, 1967, 1970-1975, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Fines (1 of 3), 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Fines (2 of 3), 1972-1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Fines (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Interrogations, 1970-1971, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. General (1 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. General (2 of 4), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. General (3 of 4), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. General (4 of 4), 1971-1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Iudintsev, Andrei, 1982 November 4 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Kholodenkov, Georgii, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Khorev, Mikhail (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Khorev, Mikhail (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Khrapov, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Kriuchkov, G., Vins, G. (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Kriuchkov, G., Vins, G. (2 of 3), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Kriuchkov, G., Vins, G. (3 of 3), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Makhovitskii, F.V., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Mashnitskii, Nikolai, 1971 July 28 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Ogorodnik, Stanislav, Goncharov, Anatolii, Tysiachuk, Aleksandr, 1974 July (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Pavlov, Iakov, 1974 February-March (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Petrov, A., 1973 September 6 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Prokofiev, A., 1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Reimer, Leongard, 1974 February 22 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Rumachik, Petr, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Shevchenko, Nikolai, Bondarenko, Iosif, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Shugalo, N., Lazuta, N., 1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Skripnikova, Aida, 1967, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Vilchinskaia, Zinaida, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Vins, Georgii, 1975 January 27-31 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Vins, Petr, 1978 April 6 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Zheltonozhko, F., Troshchenko, N., 1972 January 24-27 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Odessa Believers (1 of 2), 1967 February 6-7 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Odessa Believers (2 of 2), 1967 February 6-7 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Barnaul Believers, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Trials. Ukraine, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (1 of 17), 1965-1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (2 of 17), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (3 of 17), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (4 of 17), 1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (5 of 17), 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (6 of 17), 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (7 of 17), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (8 of 17), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (9 of 17), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (10 of 17), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (11 of 17), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (12 of 17), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (13 of 17), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (14 of 17), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (15 of 17), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (16 of 17), 1977-1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Imprisonment. General (17 of 17), 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. State Interference in Church Affairs., 1966-1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. State Interference in Church Affairs. Refusal of Registration, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. State Interference in Church Affairs. Demolition of Church Buildings, 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Mistreatment of Believers in the Army. General, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Mistreatment of Believers in the Army. Kravchenko, N., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Discrimination in Employment, 1971, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Discrimination in Education, 1972-1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Discrimination in Education. Declaration of Baptist Mothers, 1969 March (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Misuse of Psychiatry., 1973-1980 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Misuse of Psychiatry. Lazuta, Ivan, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Attacks in the Media, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. House Searches, 1970-1973, 1979, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Loss of Parental Rights (1 of 3), 1968-1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Loss of Parental Rights (2 of 3), 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Oppressive Practices Against Unregistered Baptist Believers. Loss of Parental Rights (3 of 3), 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church Life, 1974, 1977, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Individual Unregistered Baptist Church Clergy. General, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Individual Unregistered Baptist Church Clergy. Kriuchkov, Gennadii, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Individual Unregistered Baptist Church Clergy. Vins, Georgii (1 of 4), 1967-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Individual Unregistered Baptist Church Clergy. Vins, Georgii (2 of 4), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Individual Unregistered Baptist Church Clergy. Vins, Georgii (3 of 4), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Individual Unregistered Baptist Church Clergy. Vins, Georgii (4 of 4), 1975, 1977, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Individual Unregistered Baptist Church Clergy. Vins, Georgii. (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Individual Unregistered Baptist Church Clergy. Vins, Georgii. (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. International Relations, 1970, 1974, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Defense of Believers Rights. Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christian Baptist Prisoners (1 of 4), 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Defense of Believers Rights. Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christian Baptist Prisoners (2 of 4), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Defense of Believers Rights. Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christian Baptist Prisoners (3 of 4), 1970-1983 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Defense of Believers Rights. Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christian Baptist Prisoners (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Emigration on Religious Grounds. General (1 of 3), 1970, 1973-1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Emigration on Religious Grounds. General (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Emigration on Religious Grounds. General (3 of 3), 1979-1984, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Mashnitskii Family, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Sciarrino Family (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Skliarenko Family (2 of 2), 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Barnaul Church, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Vladianu Family (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Vladianu Family (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publications. General, 1967-1975, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publications. Collection of Christian Verses "Radost" ("Joy"), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publications. Publication Uzkii put'/Narrow Way, No. 1, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Information Leaflet of the Persecuted Church in Barnaul, No. 1, 1971 November (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publications. Information Leaflet of the Persecuted Church in Barnaul, No. 2, 1972 December (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Even-Ezer, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Missiia, missiia, missiia, No. 2, 1978 April-June (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2-3, 1965 February-March (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1965 April (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5-6, 1965 May-June (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 7, 1965 July (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1967 April (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5, 1967 May (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 11-12, 1967 November-December (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3, 1968 March (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5, 1968 May (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6, 1968 June (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 8, 1968 August (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 11, 1968 November (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1-2, 1969 January-February (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5, 1969 May (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 7-8, 1969 July-August (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 9-10, 1969 October-November (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 12, 1969 December (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1970 January (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1970 February (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3-4, 1970 March-April (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5, 1970 May (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6-7, 1970 June-July (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 8, 1970 August (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 9-10, 1970 September-October (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1971 April (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5-6, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 7-8, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 9-10, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 11-12, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1-3, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4-5, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4-5, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1981, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)